Jordy Morales Roman

(+591) 61787036 <u>dev.morales.jordy@gmail.com</u> <u>github.com/2jsdev</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/jordymorales</u>

Full-Stack developer

Full-Stack developer with 4+ years of experience developing web applications using JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, NodeJS, and Services (REST) applying design patterns and architectures. Experience in mobile application development. I consider myself a technology and learning enthusiast; there have never been excuses to learn something new. Looking forward to being part of an innovative team.

EXPERIENCE:

Unosquare, Bolivia — Software Developer — June 2021 - Present

Outsourcing with the Conversica company, which provides artificial intelligence solutions that help business revenue teams attract, acquire and grow customers. Where it helped maintain its internal tools and services that it provides to its clients.

• Working on the frontend and backend in different projects for clients to improve user data management, conversation management and answers.

Tech-Stack: JavaScript, ReactJS, CSS, Redux, Redux, Redux Saga, RTK query, Jest, Cypress, PHP, NodeJS.

Nearshore Code, Bolivia — Software Developer — January 2019 - June 2021

Worked on multiple web and mobile projects with different technologies, always applying the best practices so that the code has high cohesion and low coupling.

Participated in a public workshop about Rest Services, GraphQL, and Hexagonal Architectures.

Tech-Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, ReactJS, CSS, Redux, NodeJS, Express, GraphQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Jest, Docker, DigitalOcean, AWS, CI/CD, GitLab, GitHub, Bitbucket, Linux Servers.

Nuevatel SRL, Bolivia — Software Developer — August 2018 - December 2018

Took over 100% of the development of an internal system for Data Management, which handles the assignment and notification of shifts.

• The implementation of the system allowed to improve the response time to the failures of the internal processes, implementing a system of alerts by mail and sms.

Tech-Stack: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, Sendgrid, Twilio, Linux Servers.

SKILLS:

Programming Languages: (Proficient): JavaScript, TypeScript. (Familiar): Dart.

Frameworks and Tools: (*Proficient*): ReactJS, NodeJS, Express, API REST, Jest, Swagger, Git, GraphQL, Apollo Client, Apollo Server, Mongoose, Sequelize, TypeORM, AuthO, Docker. (*Familiar*): React Native, Cypress, Apache Kafka, Elasticsearch, Nginx, Certbot.

Database: SQL: PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQLite. NoSQL: MongoDB, Firestore, Firebase Realtime Database.

Cloud Computing: DigitalOcean, AWS.

Others: (*Proficient*): Agile Methodologies (SCRUM), SOLID, Hexagonal Architecture, Domain Driven Design. (*Familiar*): Microservices Architecture, Event Driven Design.

LANGUAGES:

English, Intermediate; Spanish, Native;

EDUCATION:

UCATEC – Cochabamba, Bolivia Systems engineer, Nov 2021